http://www.ccibeauty.com/privacy-policy

Hair & Salon
Furniture
All Purpose ChairsBarber ChairsDryer ChairsMatsShampoo Bowls and ChairsShampoo CabinetsStoolsStyling ChairsStyling StationsStyling CabinetsTrolleys and Carts
Equipment
Appliance HoldersDryersIronsSteamersTowel Warmers and Sterilizers
Supplies
ApparelDisinfectantChair CoversSpare Parts
Salon Package Deals
Spa & Skin Care
Furniture
All Purpose ChairsFacial BedsMassage Tables and ChairsStoolsTrolleys and Carts
Equipment
Facial SteamersLampsMulti-Function Facial MachinesSingle Function Facial MachinesTowel Warmers and Sanitizers
Supplies
Client Robes & Disposable ApparelProfessional ApparelDisinfectantProductsSpare Parts
Spa Package Deals
Nail
Furniture
Manicure TablesNail Dryer TablesNail Polish RackPedicure FurniturePedicure SpaStoolsTechnician and Client ChairsTrolley & Mobile Station
Supplies
DisinfectantSpare Parts
Equipment
Nail Dryers and Other EquipmentTowel Warmers and Sterilizers
Manicure and Pedicure Packages
Makeup & Threading
Furniture
All Purpose ChairsStations/CabinetsTrolley & Mobile Salon
Supplies
ApparelBeauty CasesDisposables
Makeup and Threading Packages
Reception Area
Furniture
Reception DesksReceptionist ChairsWaiting Area
Display & Decor
Barber PolesDecorative PiecesRetail DisplaysMagazine RacksPrivacy Screens
Reception Packages
Sales & ClearanceForms
Free Ground Shipping On Select Items!
WARRANTY  |  FAQ  |  FINANCING  |  OUR BLOG  |  ABOUT US  |  CONTACT US
SALON STYLING CHAIRS, MANICURE TABLES, BARBER CHAIRS, SPA EQUIPMENT, SALON EQUIPMENT, SALON FURNITURE, PEDICURE CHAIRS, AND SUPPLIES.ORDERING AND INFORMATION CALL: 1-800-708-0789 DURING OUR STORE HOURS OR USE OUR SECURE ONLINE SHOPPING AVAILABLE 24 HOURS A DAY
Hair & Salon
Furniture
All Purpose ChairsBarber ChairsDryer ChairsMatsShampoo Bowls and ChairsShampoo CabinetsStoolsStyling ChairsStyling StationsStyling CabinetsTrolleys and Carts
Equipment
Appliance HoldersDryersIronsSteamersTowel Warmers and Sterilizers
Supplies
ApparelDisinfectantChair CoversSpare Parts
Salon Package Deals
Spa & Skin Care
Furniture
All Purpose ChairsFacial BedsMassage Tables and ChairsStoolsTrolleys and Carts
Equipment
Facial SteamersLampsMulti-Function Facial MachinesSingle Function Facial MachinesTowel Warmers and Sanitizers
Supplies
Client Robes & Disposable ApparelProfessional ApparelDisinfectantProductsSpare Parts
Spa Package Deals
Nail
Furniture
Manicure TablesNail Dryer TablesNail Polish RackPedicure FurniturePedicure SpaStoolsTechnician and Client ChairsTrolley & Mobile Station
Supplies
DisinfectantSpare Parts
Equipment
Nail Dryers and Other EquipmentTowel Warmers and Sterilizers
Manicure and Pedicure Packages
Makeup & Threading
Furniture
All Purpose ChairsStations/CabinetsTrolley & Mobile Salon
Supplies
ApparelBeauty CasesDisposables
Makeup and Threading Packages
Reception Area
Furniture
Reception DesksReceptionist ChairsWaiting Area
Display & Decor
Barber PolesDecorative PiecesRetail DisplaysMagazine RacksPrivacy Screens
Reception Packages
Sales & ClearanceForms
Privacy PolicyTYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECTThis site only gathers personal information, such as, first and last names, addresses and email addresses, when voluntarily submitted by you.SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATIONOccasionally, with your permission, we will send marketing information to you, such as discount coupons, information about new product offerings, etc. If you do not elect to receive such materials, we will not send them to you.Companies may be engaged by our company to perform a variety of functions, such as, fulfilling orders, assisting with promotions, providing technical services for our web sites, etc. These companies may have access to personal information if needed to perform such functions. However, these companies may only use such personal information for the purpose of performing that function and may not use it for any other purpose.We do not sell, transfer or disclose personal information to third parties outside of our company.We reserve the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request, to protect the integrity of the site, to fulfill your requests, or to cooperate in any law enforcement investigation or an investigation on a matter of public safety.ACCESSYou are in control of any personal information you provide to us on-line. If at any time, you would like to correct the personal information we have about you or if you would like to change your preferences for contacts from us or on behalf of our business partners, please Contact Us.COOKIES"Cookies" are pieces of information that a web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies allow the web site to remember important information that will make your use of the site more convenient. Like most web sites, We use cookies for a variety of purposes in order to improve your on-line experience. For example, we track the total number of visitors to our site on an anonymous aggregate basis. We may also employ cookies so that we remember you when you return to the site, to keep track of the items in your shopping cart if you purchase merchandise online, to administer certain contests and sweepstakes and to help customize your web experience at our site. We may associate personal information with a cookie file in those instances.Use the options in your web browser if you do not wish to receive a cookie or if you wish to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. Click on the "Help" section of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. If you disable all cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of all the features of this web site.LINKS TO OTHER SITESWe may offer links to sites that are not operated by our company. If you visit one of these linked sites, you should review their privacy and other policies. We are not responsible for the policies and practices of other companies.CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICYFrom time to time, it may be necessary for us to change this privacy policy, so we suggest that you check here periodically. Rest assured, however, that any changes will not be retroactively applied and will not alter how we handle previously collected information.If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please Contact Us.
ABOUT USSHIPPING & DELIVERYRETURNSPRIVACY POLICYTERMS & CONDITIONSSITEMAP
CREATE AN ACCOUNTORDERS AND RETURNSBEAUTY SALON FAQFINANCINGREAD OUR BLOG
CONTACT US
NEWSLETTER
SUBSCRIBE
Copyright © 2001-2017 CONSONANCE COMPANIES, INC. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.10039 NORWALK BLVD. SANTA FE SPRINGS, CA 90670
Please wait
